{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Which year was Isaiah born ?",
      "options": ["2006", "2007", "2010", "2011"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Isaiah's last name?",
      "options": ["Brown", "Diakte", "DaiteKi", "Diakite"],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "How tall is Isaiah?",
      "options": ["5'11", "6'2", "6'1", "5'10"],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Isaiah's favorite color?",
      "options": ["Green", "Red", "Blue", "Blac"],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Isaih's mom name?",
      "options": ["Melisa", "Karen", "Melissa", "Melessa"],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "How intelligent is Isaiah?",
      "options": [
        "a bit intelligen",
        "intelligent",
        "very intelligent",
        " very very intelligent"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "When Isaiah sets his mind on something does he do it?",
      "options": [
        "Some time",
        "Not really",
        "He always get the job done ",
        "procrastinate and lazy"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "In which state does Isaiah live at?",
      "options": ["California", "New-York", "Ohio", "Idiana"],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "What was Isaiah's Primary School name?",
      "options": [
        " town scholl",
        "Ecole b",
        "When we need to add styles",
        "Longfellow"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "What best describe Isaiah?",
      "options": [
        "Very lazy ",
        "some time lazy some time hard worker",
        "I don't know it's hard to tell",
        "don't like to leave his comfort zone",
        "A go getter, very smart and goal oriented"
      ],
      "correctOption": 4,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 'Isaiah's race?",
      "options": ["white", "Latino", "Human", "Black"],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "How much does Isaiah's dad loves him?",
      "options": [
        "a bit ",
        "very much",
        "very very much like billion * billion * billion that much and more",
        "like him very much"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 10
    }
  ]
}
